Guide to the Duke University Oral History Program Collection, 1973-1978, 1992 RL.00338
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Oral History Program collection
1973-1978, 1992 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Oral History Program
RL.00338
10.3 Linear Feet
810 Items
Access Restrictions
The Duke University Oral History Program Collection has been restricted due to the absence of release forms transferring intellectual property rights from interviewees or interviewers to researchers using the collections. Researchers are cautioned that the publication of information contained in these interviews may violate the legal rights of the interviewees and interviewers. It is the sole responsibility of researchers to secure permission from interviewees or interviewers to publish quotes from either, and to ensure that information gained from research in this collection is not used in any way that violates rights remaining with interviewees, interviewers, or their heirs. Patrons who wish to use this collection must sign a Restricted Materials Research Agreement, which may be obtained from any Special Collections reference staff person.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Duke University Oral History Program Collection (1973-1978, 1992, & undated) was donated to the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library in 1983, 1992 and 1993 by William H. Chafe, Oral History Program, History Department Duke University, and in 1992 and 1993 by Timothy Tyson.
Collection Overview
The Duke University Oral History Program Collection contains 238 oral history interviews conducted by project participants in the years 1973-1978 and 1992. The majority of the oral history interviews deal with the civil rights movement in North Carolina, especially Durham, Chapel Hill, and Greensboro. Additionally, thirteen interviews deal with the Tulsa Race Riots, and fourteen interviews cover miscellaneous North Carolina topics. The collection also includes transcripts and research files related to the civil rights movement in North Carolina.
The collection is arranged in three series: Audiotapes, Transcripts, and Research Files. The Audiotapes Series consists of two identical sets of audiocassettes, one closed for preservation purposes and one open for researchers. The North Carolina Civil Rights Movement tapes, which make up the bulk of the series, include extensive interviews with Ella Baker, as well as hundreds of interviews with lesser-known but nonetheless important figures from the local movements in Greensboro, Durham, Chapel Hill, Weldon, and Monroe, N.C. The Tulsa Race Riots tapes include interviews conducted by Scott Ellsworth for his study Death in the Promised Land: The Tulsa Race Riot of 1921. The North Carolina Miscellaneous tapes include an interview with Alex Haley about his critically-acclaimed book, Roots, as well as conversations about such topics as the state's agricultural history and mountain culture in Western North Carolina. The Transcripts Series includes eighty transcripts, as well as some interview notes, corresponding to tapes dealing with the North Carolina civil rights movement. The Research Files Series contains six files of background material related to the civil rights movement in North Carolina, including articles and speeches by Governor Terry Sanford and a bibliography of material dealing with the Durham sit-ins, and one file listing tapes and transcripts in the collection.
Tulsa (Okla.) -- Race relations; Tulsa (Okla.) -- Riot, 1921; Civil rights -- North Carolina -- Monroe; African Americans -- Civil rights -- North Carolina; Civil rights -- North Carolina -- History; Oral history; Civil rights -- North Carolina -- Greensboro; Civil rights -- North Carolina -- Durham; Civil rights -- North Carolina -- Chapel Hill; Duke University Oral History Program; Baker, Ella
- North Carolina Civil Rights Movement, 1973-1992; 1
  Scope and Contents
  The majority of these tapes deal with the civil rights movement in Chapel Hill, Greensboro and Durham, and their environs, and include extensive interviews with Ella Baker. The twenty-eight interviews conducted by Marcellus Barksdale in 1976 and 1977 predominantly cover the movement in Weldon and Monroe, N.C. These interviews formed part of the basis for his 1977 Ph.D. dissertation, The Indigenous Civil Rights Movement and Cultural Change in North Carolina: Weldon, Chapel Hill, and Monroe, 1946-1965. Larry Thomas and Timothy Tyson's eleven interviews, conducted in 1978 and 1992, respectively, deal with the civil rights movement in Monroe. Tyson drew on these interviews for his 1994 Ph.D. dissertation, Radio Free Dixie: Robert F. Williams and the Roots of Black Power.
  - Adams, Charlotte - interviewed by Fred Baldwin, 1974-08-21; 2
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0187)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0303)
  - Albright, Reverend J.W. - interviewer unidentified, 1974-01-31; 3
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0188)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0304)
  - Arrington, Marvin; Cochran, Salter J. - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1976-10-08; 4
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0173)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0084)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0174)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0085)
  - Ashby, Warren - interviewed by William Chafe, 1974-10-03; 5
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0190)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0306)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0189)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0305)
  - Atwater, Ann - interviewed by Harriott Quin, 1977-11-23; 6
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0191)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0307)
  - Atwater, Lula - interviewer unidentified, circa 1974; 7
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0192)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0308)
  - Augustine, Joe - interviewed by Leon Fink, 1974-06-14; 8
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0194)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0310)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0193)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0309)
  - Baker, Ella - interviewer unidentified, 1976-11-27; 9
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 4 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0001)
    - Audio reel preservation master, tape 1 of 4 (Box 3, Audio-reel RL00338-RR-0001)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 4 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0005)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 4 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0002)
    - Audio reel preservation master, tape 2 of 4 (Box 3, Audio-reel RL00338-RR-0002)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 4 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0006)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 3 of 4 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0003)
    - Audio reel preservation master, tape 3 of 4 (Box 3, Audio-reel RL00338-RR-0003)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 3 of 4 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0007)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 4 of 4 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0004)
    - Audio reel preservation master, tape 4 of 4 (Box 3, Audio-reel RL00338-RR-0004)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 4 of 4 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0008)
  - Baker, Quinton - interviewed by Larry Goodwyn, 1974-06-02; 10
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0195)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0311)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0196)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0312)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0197)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0313)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0198)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0314)
  - Banks, Daniel (pseudonym?) - interviewed by Larry Thomas, 1978-05-14; 11
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0112)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0023)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0113)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0024)
  - Bazemore, P.E. - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-05-01; 12
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0175)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0086)
  - Belton, Edward - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-04-30; 13
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0176)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0087)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0177)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0088)
  - Black Duke Students and Employees, White Duke Students and Employees - interviewer unidentified, circa 1974; 14
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0199)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0315)
  - Bordeaux, Walter - interviewed by Larry Thomas, 1978-08-11; 15
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0114)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0025)
  - Boulware, C.E. - interviewed by Harriott Quin, 1977-11-04; 16
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0200)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0316)
  - Bowers, Wayne; Bowers, Mary - interviewed by Tina Harrison and Bill Bishop, 1974-06-06; 17
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0201)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0317)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0202)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0318)
  - Bowles, Mrs. Charles - interviewed by William Chafe, 1974-09-24; 18
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0203)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0319)
  - Brown, Bob - interviewed by Ken Hamilton, 1974-06-06; 19
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0204)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0320)
  - Bulkley, Joel - interviewed by William Chafe, 1974-06-14; 20
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0205)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0321)
  - Bynum, Barbara - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale and Eric Perkins, 1974-06-05; 21
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0206)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0322)
  - Bynum, Sheila - interviewed by Janice Carr, 1974-06-05; 22
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0207)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0323)
  - "C-Man" - interviewed by Larry Thomas, 1978-08-12;1978-08-16; 1
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0115)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0026)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0116)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0027)
  - Caldwell, Edwin Sr. - interviewed by Tina Harrison, 1974-08-28; 23
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0208)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0324)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0209)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0325)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 3 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0210)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 3 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0326)
  - Caldwell, Hilliard - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-04-26; 24
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0178)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0089)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0212)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0327)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0328)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0211)
  - Calhoun, Dick - interviewed by Romus Broadway and Bill Bishop, 1974-06-04; 25
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0213)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0329)
  - Campbell, J.A.; Cofield, A.C. - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-05-06;1977-05-07; 26
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0179)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0090)
  - Campbell, Sharon Sitton; taped reminiscences sent to Jake Phelps -, circa 1974; 27
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0214)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0330)
  - Carswell, John - interviewed by Lois Gilman and Wendy Watriss, circa 1974; 28
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0215)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0331)
  - Clarence and wife - interviewed by Dick Landeman, 1974-06-16; 29
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0216)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0332)
  - Clark, A.D. - interviewed by Tina Harrison, 1974-06-12; 30
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0217)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0333)
  - Clemonts, James; Boone, Michael - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1976-10-07;1976-10-08; 31
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0180)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0091)
  - Cobb, Collier III - interviewed by Leon Fink, 1974-06-12; 32
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0218)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0334)
  - Cochran, Doris - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-02-17; 33
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0181)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0092)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0182)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0093)
  - Cofield, Augustus C. and his daughter - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1976-10-06; 34
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0183)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0094)
  - Coleman, Gus - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-02-10; 35
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0184)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0095)
  - Cosby, Wesley; Matthews, Mrs. A.C. - intervied by Marcellus Barksdale, 1976-10-07;1976-10-08; 36
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0185)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0096)
  - Cotton, Charlie Pearl - interviewed by Wayne Watson and Wendy Watriss, circa 1974; 37
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0219)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0335)
  - Curitan, William - interviewed by Ken Hamilton, 1974-08-25; 38
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0220)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0336)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0221)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0337)
  - Cusick, Pat - interviewed by group, 1974-06-10; 39
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 4 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0222)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 4 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0338)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 4 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0223)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 4 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0339)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 3 of 4 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0224)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 3 of 4 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0340)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 4 of 4 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0225)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 4 of 4 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0341)
  - Dansby, David - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1974-06-06; 40
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0226)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0342)
  - Dowdy, Lewis - interviewed by William Chafe, 1975-06-21; 41
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0227)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0343)
  - Dunne, John - interviewed by group, 1974-06-08; 42
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0229)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0345)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0228)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0344)
  - Evans, Mrs. Docea - interviewer unidentified, 1974-01-16; 43
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0230)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0346)
  - Faison, John W. - interviewed by Marcellus Barksdale, 1977-05-07; 44
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0186)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0097)
  - Fitts, Howard - interviewed by Harriott Quin, 1977-12-01; 45
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0231)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0347)
  - Foster, Haddie B. - interviewed by Tina Harrison, 1974-08-26; 46
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0232)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0348)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0233)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0349)
  - Foster, Harold - interviewed by Ken Hamilton, 1974-08-26; 47
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0234)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0350)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0235)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0351)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 3 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0236)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 3 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0352)
  - Foster, John; Coley, Nell; Troxler, Kay - interviewed by William Chafe, 1974-10-15; 48
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0237)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0353)
  - Foushee, Braxton - interviewed by Romus Broadway and Bill Bishop, 1974-06-05; 49
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0238)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0354)
  - Foushee, Charles - interviewed by Ken Hamilton, 1974-06-05; 50
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0239)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0355)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0240)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0356)
  - Foushee, James - interviewed by Ken Hamilton and Tina Harrison, 1974-06-09; 51
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0241)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0357)
  - Foushee, Vivian - interviewed by Tina Harrison and Leon Fink, 1974-06-04; 52
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0242)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0358)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0244)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0359)
  - Foushee, W.M. - interviewed by Fred Baldwin and Eric Perkins, 1974-06-04; 53
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0245)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0361)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0246)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0362)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0248)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0364)
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0247)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0363)
  - French, Virginia - interviewed by Wayne Watson and Wendy Watriss, 1974-06-05; 54
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0249)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0365)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0250)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0366)
  - Giduz, Roland - interviewed by Wendy Watriss, 1974-08-26; 55
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0251)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0367)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 3 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0252)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 3 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0368)
  - Grant, Jim - interviewed by Larry Thomas, 1978-07-10; 56
    - Audiocassette original (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0117)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0028)
  - Gulick, Margaret - interviewed by Lois Gilman, 1974-06-06; 57
    - Audiocassette original, tape 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0254)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 1 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0369)
    - Audiocassette original, tape 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0255)
    - Audiocassette backup copy, tape 2 of 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0370)
  - Harris, Maggie Scott - interviewer unidentified, 1974-01-31; 58
    - Audiocassette original (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0257)
    - Audiocassette backup copy (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00338-CS-0372)